## Aaron Zomback

Hello, I'm Aaron. I'm a self-taught filmmaker, software developer and UX designer. I'm a highly motivated individual who can learn things quickly and I enjoy collaborating in a team environment. My goal is to apply my creative skills towards transforming educational experiences (especially science education) through storytelling and VR.

3 Chemin de Gage Chazay-d'Azergues, France aaronzomback@gmail.com +33 6 29 81 98 34





#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Freelance Software Developer and UX Designer Chazay d'Azergues, FR

March 2020 - present

I've been hired to work for a variety of successful clients, from designing a food takeout app for a start-up, a boutique t-shirt company, to redesigning a restaurant point-of-sale system. My complete portfolio can be found at www.zomback.design. I am also an active member of the Interaction-Design Foundation.

### Sr. Research Associate Scientist, Calder Biosciences Brooklyn, NY

November 2014 - October 2019

Designed and conducted experiments targeting vaccine candidates for HIV, RSV (Respiratory Syncytial Virus) & Influenza.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SuperHi, online courses

December 2019 - May 2020

Visual Design & Branding, Intro to User Experience, Foundations HTML/CSS/JavaScript, Command Line for Creatives, Ruby-on-Rails

#### University of Washington, Seattle, WA – Biochemistry B.S.

September 2009 - June 2014

Distinction: awarded Mary Gates Research Scholarship for host-virus research work in Dr. Harmit Malik's lab.

#### **SKILLS**

CODING Ruby on
Rails/Command
Line/CSS/JS/HTML/Git &
GitHub foundational coding
knowledge and applications.

UX/UI DESIGN Building interactive mobile/web prototypes in Figma. Other deliverables include: user-flows, empathy mapping, user research, SWOT competitive analysis, site maps, google analytics, et al. It's all about the process, knowing which tools to use, and how the story is told.

VIDEO motion effects and graphics editing using Adobe After Effects. Expert with Adobe Premiere Cs6+

communication strong experience in working with clients to achieve their business goals. I have strong experience presenting scientific data, collaborating with other researchers and colleagues, & planning strategies to achieve business objectives.

## SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS strong knowledge in a suite of

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

# Prefusion RSV F Immunization Elicits Th2-Mediated Lung Pathology in Mice

<sup>4</sup>Aaron Zomback, et al, Frontiers Immunology, 29 July 2020

https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fimmu.2020.01673/full

#### **PROJECTS**

#### TimeSink™ – A web app for an online cinema platform

Designing and developing an online platform for filmmakers to present their work and receive user reviews. I am writing the application using Ruby on Rails.

#### **FILMS**

## Sovereign Blue-2018, short film

My second short film that I created while I was living and working in Brooklyn, NY - I wrote, produced, and directed this short, featuring Rodney Ferrer as the maniacal CEO of a multi-media company. A review of the film can be found <a href="https://example.com/here">here</a> at UK Film Review.

### Expanded Metal – 2016, short film

My first short film that I created. It later went on to screen at the 2017 Philip K. Dick Science Fiction film festival in New York City.

tools: Figma, Framer, Command Line, Git & GitHub, GraphPad Prism 6, SeqBuilder, Excel, Word, Powerpoint, Figma, Photoshop, Premiere Pro.

LABORATORY experimental design and execution, safety protocols, mastery of tools such as pipettes, filters, TFF & column purifications, measurements, inventory, note-taking, and analysis.

#### **AWARDS**

Mary Gates Research Scholarship Viral & Host Protein Interaction Research

#### **LANGUAGES**

English (native), French (learning), Spanish (proficiency)